botmasterlabs.net 2019-06-24

# BotmasterLabs.Net: Privacy Policy and "Cookies" Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. 

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience. 

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site. 

## How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To quickly process your transactions. 
  * To iddentify you as legal buyer of product. 

## How do we protect your information?

We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers. 

All stored information are encripted. 

## Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

We use cookies to: 

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. 

If you turn cookies off, It won't affect the user's experience. 

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## Third-party links

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website. 

We collect your email address in order to: 

  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders. 
  * Send you additional information related to your product and/or service 

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below. 

Botmaster Labs  
Czech Republic  
sales@botmasterlabs.cz
